<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Overview on JEFFRIS</title>
    <link>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Overview on JEFFRIS</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Download the Code</title>
      <link>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/code-downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/code-downloads/</guid>
      <description>There are three Github repositories for this project, as follows:   NameLinkPurpose  student-image-processing https://github.com/bwsi-hadr/student-image-processing Process Images using Python and OpenCV, and show the analysis in Flask.   student-access-images https://github.com/bwsi-hadr/student-access-images Use MongoDB to store Raspberry Pi images to a database, and create methods to open them in the Flask application.   student-pi-imaging https://github.com/bwsi-hadr/student-pi-imaging Take time lapse images on the Raspberry Pi during flights.    Creating Forks of the Repositories  Open the image processing repository above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repository Configurations</title>
      <link>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/repository-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 19:27:37 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/repository-config/</guid>
      <description>Add the Upstream To properly set up your github repositories, you will need to set the MIT code repositories as your upstreams. While the origin repository represents code that you write, the upstream repository is the original repostiory that your code &amp;ldquo;works off of.&amp;rdquo; At first, it may seem like you don&amp;rsquo;t need to use the upstream anymore, since you already have the code. However, this is an important step because if the upstream code changes, adding the upstream allows you to update your code to match the most recent state of the upstream.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git Workflow</title>
      <link>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/git-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://intermezzio.github.io/JEFFRIS/docs/git-workflow/</guid>
      <description> Summary Staging files Commits Push Pull Merge Troubleshooting </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>